# REY CAL

♥ SUNNYBANK, 4109, AUSTRALIA 

■ 0412639474

#### · DETAILS ·

13 Sunnybrae St SUNNYBANK, 4109 Australia 0412639474

#### caiyingzhengrey@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth 2002 03 06 China

> Nationality Chinese

Driving license None

# SKILLS

Quick Hand

Patiend and friendly attitude

Kitechen skills

Remain calm under pressure

Careful

Hard Working

Respectful and communication

Follow the instructions/obedient

LANGUAGES

Chinese

English

#### · HOBBIES ·

Basket ball and all kinds of sports. Music, playing guitar and singing. Play video games and all kinds of card games/board games.

## ♣ PROFILE

My name is Rey and is currently studying the bachelor of Information Technology at the University of Queensland. I am 19 years old now and is holding student VISA at the moment. I have been in Australia for 3 years now, and I have been working part-time job for a long time. My past work experiences are mostly kitchen-hand, cashier and waiter.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

#### Cashier and Waitor at Kung Food Noodle, Pinelands

February 2019 - September 2019

- Independent worker since the whole restaurant except kitchen is managed by myself.
- Learn how to use the cashier machine and some basic kitchen skill.
- · Served as a friendly, hardworking, and punctual employee.
- · Remained flexible, adaptable, and calm under pressure.

## Waitor at The Cube Hot Pot, Sunnybank

November 2019 - January 2020

- · Friendly worker and nice and patient attitude to customers.
- Operated with a strong work ethic, professionalism, and the ability to work under pressure.

## Waitor and Kitchen-Hand at IThai restaurant, Sunnybank

January 2020 - February 2021

- · Served as a friendly, hardworking, and punctual employee.
- · Worked as a positive and hardworking team member in a busy environment.

#### Kitchen-Hand and Dish Washer at Sushi Kivo, Coorparoo

January 2021 - June 2021

- · Friendly and patient with the customers and other employees.
- Remained adaptable, flexible, and calm in high-pressure environments.
- · Quick hand and well-organized attitude under high-pressure customer flow.
- · Maintained a clean and organized working environment to enhance productivity.
- W

#### EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Technology, University of Queensland, St Lucia February 2021 — November 2023

High school Graduates, Groves Christian College, Kingston July 2018 — December 2020

High School Preparation and English Certification, Browns English Language School,

January 2018 - July 2018

Brisbane central